ubridge.org 2019-05-04

# Privacy Policy - University Bridge

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) governs your use of [89.238.212.158](http://www.ubridge.org/) and our other websites on which this Privacy Policy is posted (the “Websites”) and explains, in general, what Personal Information (as defined below) and other information is collected on the Websites, how the information is used and with whom we may share such information. CollegeSolved, LLC is referred to in this Privacy Policy as the “Company,” “we,” “us,” “our” or other similar pronouns.

We take your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy explains what we do to make as sure as reasonably possible that information about you is kept both secure and confidential. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, as once you use our website or our services you will be deemed to have read and accepted this Privacy Policy.

By visiting the Websites and/or by using the services available on the Websites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. As we update and expand our services and technology changes and improves, this Privacy Policy may change, so we recommend that you check back to this page from time to time. If we make material changes, we will notify you here, by email or by means of a notice on our homepage. All information collected after any updates to the Privacy Policy will be subject to the new policy.

**Purpose**

Your privacy is important to us. In order to make your visits to our Websites and use of the services available through our Websites as worthwhile as possible, we may ask you for Personal Information and we may collect certain information from your computer each time you visit the Websites. “ **Personal Information** ” includes, for example, your name; home and/or business address; e-mail address; telephone, wireless and/or fax number; short message service or text message address or other wireless device address; instant messaging address; credit card and other payment information; demographic information, educational and scholastic information and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual.

We collect information about our users for a variety of purposes. These include the following:

  * where users supply data to us in relation to educational services that we offer (for example, to apply for the University Bridge program (“University Bridge”) or to obtain information about University Bridge), data will be processed by us to supply the information requested by our users. Your information is held by the Company in the United States;
  * so that we can inform our users of new offers, products, and services which may be of interest to them; and
  * so that we can send our users news and marketing items which are relevant to their interests to help us improve and personalize the services provided to our users.

**What Information is Collected on the Websites?**

User-Provided Information

We collect Personal Information from users of our Websites, for example, through such users’ activities, transactions and completion of online forms on our Websites. Such information may be collected, for example, when users create profiles, register or subscribe for accounts or features on our Websites, enter into online transactions, complete surveys, provide college reviews, respond to polls, input information into our interactive programming features such as our interactive calendar and search engine, submit content, including without limitation, media files, photos, videos, documents or other information to the Websites, contribute to a chat room, list serve, blog or other open forum or community feature that we may make available on our Websites, submit a comment or question to us using a “contact us” or similar feature on our Websites, send us an e-mail, view web pages, advertisements or file attachments, or in any other way submit Personal Information to us via our Websites.

You may be able to send information about our products and services to your friends and family members through our Websites by clicking on a “Share with a Friend” or similar button on our Websites or in an e-mail that we have sent you. In some of these cases (unless you simply forward our e-mail on your own), you may be able to provide the name and e-mail address of your friend or family member to us. If you have a Gmail account and have given us permission to access your Gmail address book to make suggestions about friends or family members you may want to send such messages to, you understand that CollegeSolved may access your Gmail account address book for such purposes. Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

**Website Usage Information**

Cookies

We may use “cookies” to keep, and sometimes track, information about you. Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser or related software from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies track where you travel on our Websites and what you look at and purchase. They may store your username and/or password. A cookie may enable us to relate your use of our Websites to other information about you, including your Personal Information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on our Websites. Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Websites or certain areas or features of the Websites.

Clear GIFs

We may use “clear GIFs” (aka “Web beacons” or “pixel tags”) or similar technologies, in the Websites and/or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a Web page or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a Web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual’s viewing or receipt of a Web page or message. A clear GIF may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a Web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information.

IP Address and Clickstream Data

Our servers automatically collect data about your server’s Internet address when you visit us. This information is known as an IP Address, and is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider. When you request pages from our Websites, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our servers may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another Website or a search engine); the pages you visit on our Websites; the Website you visit after our Websites; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of Web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on our Websites or a referral site; and other Web usage activity and data logged by our Web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Websites. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may also link this information with your Personal Information.

Any or all of these activities with regard to Website Usage Information may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.

**How is Personal Information Used?**

We will use the Personal Information you provide to our Websites, for example, to respond to your requests and to provide you with our services and features. We may also use your Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Website Usage Information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties.

In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings and the like) and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt out of receiving such correspondence by following the instructions in the **Right to Opt In and Opt Out** section.

We may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Website and e-mails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate.

**Do We Share Personal Information and Website Usage Information With Others?**

Public Forums & Submitted Content

When you contribute to a public area or similar feature of our Websites, such as a chat room, bulletin board, survey, list serve, blog, wiki or other open forum that we may make available on or through our Websites, or when you contribute content to any of our Websites, the information that you submit may be made available to other users of the Websites as well as the general public. For this reason, we recommend that you do not include any sensitive information on, or in your submissions to, these areas of our Websites, including, for example, your full name, home address, phone number, social security number, financial information or other information that would enable other users to locate you.

Service Providers

We may use third-party partners to help operate or promote our Websites and deliver our products and services, and may share your information with our affiliates, service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through the Websites or for our business (such as Website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, licensees of our data and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf).

Aggregate Statistics

We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Websites and e-mails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user.

Legally Compelled Disclosures

We may disclose user information (which may include Personal Information) to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Websites, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

Business Transfers

In the event that we, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets.

Third-Party Ad Servers

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Websites. These companies may use information about you and your visits to our and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies also may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses’ privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your Website Usage Information or Personal Information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative’s consumer Website at http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/.

**Transferring your information abroad**

Information supplied to us by you will only be transferred abroad by us or our partners for the purpose of performing contractual obligations owed by us to you; for example, to supply an educational agent in your country or region with your information to enable that agent to provide you with services you require.

**Security**

We endeavor to protect the security and integrity of all sensitive Personal Information provided to us via our Websites. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

If you contact us by e-mail or a “contact us” or similar feature on our Websites, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit.

You may be able to create an account on our Websites with a username and password. If so, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any access to or use of the Websites by you or any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security. We will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this provision, nor will we have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, if we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification. If you prefer for us to use another method to notify you in this situation, please e-mail us at [privacy@collegesolved.com](mailto:%20privacy@collegesolved.com) with the alternative contact information you wish to be used.

**Consent to Processing**

By providing Personal Information to our Websites, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories.

**Children under 13 Years of Age**

We do not knowingly collect identifiable information online from children under the age of 13. If a child provides us with type of information online, please contact us to have the account deactivitated by sending an email to [privacy@collegesolved.com](mailto:privacy@collegesolved.com).

**Third-Party “Linked-To” Websites**

When you are on our Websites you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other sites not operated by us. These sites may collect Personal Information from and about you. Company does not control such Websites and is not responsible for the privacy and information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not address the privacy and information practices of those other Websites.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of our Websites by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Websites. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Websites or sending you an e-mail.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may contact us at [privacy@collegesolved.com](mailto:%20privacy@collegesolved.com).

Last Updated: October 31, 2013
